

CONTACT



9822497271



omgempires60@gmail.com



Bardiya, Nepal



jitendrachaudhary

EDUCATION

Pre-Diploma in CSAD IT Information Technology

NAME Technical College/ Nepalgunj / August, 2022

+2

In 2078 I completed my +2 study from Shree Nepal Rastriya Namuna Secondary School, Bardiya

SKILLS

- Frontend Web Developer and PHP-Experience
- Graphics Designing Experience
- Basic Computer Knowledge Expert

LANGUAGE

Nepali

English

Hindi



Jitendra Chaudhary

About Me

I have a skilled and experienced for Frontend Developer with a passion for creating engaging and immersive website experiences. I have 1 years of experience in the web development industry, and have worked on a variety of projects. Also have experience in Basic computer knowledge with a strong background in operating and maintaining about computer.

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer



2021 - Present

I will make multiple sample of design in designing field.

Frontend Web Developer



2022 - Present

I work as a GK IT Solution Company where I make a sample personal website.

Basic Computer Teacher



2023 - Present

I work as a it teacher at Name Technical College where I make sure my students get enough knowledge from me about computer.

PROJECTS



Build a Personal Website

I was making project while creating this system. We created this website to manage the overall activities of web sample.

Build a E-Commerce Website

I was making project while creating this system. We created this E-Commerce Website to manage the overall activities of other online sample.